我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For five years,I was stranded on an
island with only one goal... survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and
bring down those who are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
下次你女儿和义务警员联系时
我们能一字不漏地监听
Next time your daughter calls the
Vigilante,we'll be able to listen to every word.
我知道你发誓要抓住他 警长
I know you swore to bring
this guy down,detective,
可用女儿当诱饵 太冷血了吧
but using your own daughter
as bait,that's stone cold.
- 哪来的
- 你继父给我的
- Where'd you get it?
- From your stepfather.
他从哪得来的
And where did he get it?
你妈那
Belongs to your mother.
嗨 George
Hi,George.
- Vanch
- 见到我很惊讶吗
- Vanch...
- Surprised to see me?
我想你应该在观望如何搞砸我的审讯
I imagine you would be,seeing
as how you botched my trial,
Viv说这是在维护我的利益
and from what Viv here tells
me,protecting my interests.
有不可预测的因素介入嘛
There were contingencies
that couldn't be anticipated.
没错 Vivian和我说了
Yes,Vivian told me.
三合会的头被暴露了
Bertinelli也被抓了
The head of the Triad getting
ventilated,Bertinelli getting collared,
还有那个弓箭手
and,uh,this archer.
是啊
Exactly.
碰到这种事我该怎么办呢
What am I supposed to do in
the face of something like that?
什么都不用做 Georgie 这么说吧
Absolutely nothing,Georgie.
Tell you what.
啥都不怪你 抱一个
All is forgiven. Give us a hug.
来
Come on.
我可以找个地方待一段时间
缓缓我的晕船 George
You know,I could use a place to stay while
I'm getting my sea legs back under me,George.
你这地方不错
And you got a nice place here.
怎么说 George
What do you say? George?
George
George?
希望George买了食物
I hope George has been food shopping.
我可饿坏了
I'm famished.
这个本子是你在猎捕的人的名单
So this book contains a list of the
names of the guys you've been hunting.
而你妈的这本 有同样的名单
And this book,your mother's,has
the same list of names.
完全一样
It's identical.
你妈是从哪得来的 Oliver
So where'd your mother
get her copy,Oliver?
说到这个 这本是谁给你的
For that matter,who gave it to you?
Felicity Smoak
Felicity Smoak.
她说Walter在他们房间里发现的
She said that Walter
found it in their bedroom.
现在他失踪了
And now he's missing.
她是我妈 Diggle
She's my mother,Diggle.
- 她不是那种能够...
- 让她丈夫消失的人吗
- She's not the kind of person who would...
- Have her husband disappeared?
问题就在这里 Oliver
Because that's really the
question,isn't it,Oliver?
我理解相对于继父你更相信你母亲
I understand why you would believe
your mother over your stepfather,
但我更愿相信失踪的那方
或者假设已死的那方
but I tend to believe the innocent party
is whoever's missing... and presumed dead.
动一下我就割了你的喉
Twitch,and I will open your throat.
有多少人跟着你
How many more with you?
什么
What?!
给你十秒说服我 不然我就杀了你
You have ten seconds to tell me something
I believe before I cut out your voice box.
等等
Wait,wait,wait.
姚飞让我来这的 我确定你不会杀我的
Yao Fei sent me here,and I'm pretty
sure it wasn't so you could kill me.
什么
What?
姚飞
Yao Fei.
他给了我你飞机的位置
He gave me directions to your... plane.
Frank 你跟我开玩笑吧
Frank,you got be kidding me.
你现在可不能给我别的任务
You can't throw me
another assignment now.
是副官的意思
我很确定他给了我这个权力
It's Lieutenant,and I'm pretty sure
that's what gives me the authority.
帽衫侠的调查日渐清晰了
I'm drawing in on the
Hood investigation.
我能抓到那个混蛋
I am going to get this bastard.
你没想过没人想要你这么做吗
Have you considered the
possibility no one wants you to?
什么
What?
他在圣诞节救了人质
He saved the Christmas hostages.
他拿下了纵火犯和开装甲车的贼
He took down an arsonist
and armored car thieves,
上周他还捣毁了
我们根本抓不到的毒品集团
and just last week,he busted the
Vertigo drug ring when we couldn't.
都市传奇成为英雄了
What was urban legend's becoming heroic.
这人称得上英雄的话
我不知道我身为警察的意义何在
If this man's a hero,I don't know what
my life in this city as a cop means.
那我建议你服从命令
Let me suggest you find
meaning in following orders.
Frank 听着
Frank,listen!
我已经很靠近了
I'm close.
如果我能再查到些...
If my lead comes to something more...
Quentin 拿点有用的来 我们再谈
Come to me with something
real,Quentin,and we'll talk.
同时你还得接新的案子
In the meantime,I'm
assigning you another case.
准备出去吗
Heading out?
是的 和财政规划员的一个会
Oh,yeah,it's a meeting
with the financial planners.
有什么事吗
Are you all right?
我想和你谈一件事
There was something that I
wanted to talk to you about.
想和你谈谈Walter
I want to talk to you about Walter.
圣诞节那会 他消失的时候 给了我这个
Right around Christmas,when
he...disappeared,he gave me this.
这是你爸的笔记本
This is your father's notebook.
他把斯特林市所有
欠他人情的人列了个名单
He kept a list of all the people in
Starling City who owed him favors.
我不知道竟然有这么多
I had...no idea there
was so many of them.
我在网上查了这些人
他们都不是什么好人
I've just been researching some of those
names online,and,um,they're not good people.
Oliver
我不知道你爸跟这些人有什么关系
Oliver,I have no idea what your
father was involved in or with whom.
你和你妹妹都知道
他其实并没有对我坦诚
And you and your sister both now know
that he wasn't exactly honest with me.
- 那我们就得找出...
- 不
- Then we need to find out...
- no.
如果你说的是真的
这个名单上都是坏人
If what you say is true and this
list is filled with bad people
Walter又在调查 而他现在...
and Walter was looking
into it,and now he...
要让这个家庭安全的唯一办法
The only way to keep this family safe is
就是所有人不许再有任何疑问
包括你 Oliver
for everyone in it to stop asking
questions,including you,Oliver.
答应我
Promise me.
这是真的诶
So this is really happening.
498小时的社区服务
498 hours of community service to go.
499小时 这个报到会不算
499. This orientation doesn't count.
告诉我这不是残酷惩罚
Tell me how this is not
cruel and unusual punishment.
Anastasia 向你介绍下
我们的新实习生 Thea Queen
Anastasia,I'd like you to
meet our new intern,Thea Queen.
实习生是有学校信誉的
我更像法庭派遣的奴隶
Interns get school credit. I'm
more like a court-ordered slave.
我赞同
I can relate.
Anastasia现在是在她律所
给的无偿休假期间
Anastasia is on a one year pro-bono
sabbatical from her law firm.
没有六位数的薪水
And apparently from
my six figure salary.
帮助他人的经历就是酬劳所在
The experience of helping
others is its own reward.
我还没看到任何证据能证明
I have yet to see any evidence of that.
说到缺少证据
Cyrus Vanch被释放了
And speaking a lack of evidence,Cyrus
Vanch was released from Iron Heights.
我们代表维护受害者组织
准备把Vanch再关进去
We represent a victim's advocacy group
who's trying to keep Vanch locked up.
- 我去联系Kate Spencer
- 我已经联系过了
- I'm calling Kate Spencer.
- I already did.
她说没有进一步证据之前
地检也无能为力
She said there's nothing the D.A.'s
office can do without further evidence.
我去她办公室说
Well,then I'm going to her office.
她还说不要去她办公室
And then she also said not
to show up at her office.
Vanch有过人口贩卖 毒品交易 敲诈勒索
Vanch is connected to human
trafficking,drug running,racketeering,
还有至少52项杀人罪
and at least 52 different homicides.
好吧 那你准备怎么办
除非你有私家警队
Ok,so what's the play? Because unless you
have access to some private police force,
Vanch还是能逍遥法外
Vanch will stay free
to roam the streets.
我得接个电话 喂
I have to get this. Hello?
晚上和我还有一堆有名大厨过如何
How does a night with me and
a dozen famous chefs sound?
就像"亿万未婚夫"里的桥段吗
Like an episode of "The Bachelor".
明晚我要面试俱乐部的大厨
I'm auditioning potential chefs
for the club tomorrow night.
我预约了一次试吃
多个人帮忙尝也不错哦
I've arranged a tasting,and I could
use an extra set of taste buds.
我在想办法让一个重犯回监狱
没时间呢
I'm trying to figure out how to get a
vicious criminal back in jail. I can't.
很好啊 像是很饥渴的工作
It's perfect. It
sounds like hungry work.
明晚吧
Tomorrow night?
也许我们能早点完工
Maybe,if we could do it early.
我得挂了
Look,I got to go.
我还要打给另一个人
There's someone I have to call.
晚点见 拜
I'll see you later. Bye.
你没觉得这太轻易了吗
You don't find that a little convenient,
她就这么烧了那本本子
her just so happening
to have burned the book?
她是出于我的安全考虑 Diggle
She did it out of concern
for my safety,Diggle.
或是她自己的 Oliver 你自己说过
Or her own. Oliver,you said it yourself.
列这个名单的人有危险因素
Whoever compiled that list is
involved in something very dangerous.
如果你妈在骗你
And if your mother is lying to you...
她不知道名单上的名字
And she didn't know any
of the names on the list.
她自己说不知道
She said she didn't.
你不用相信她
You don't have to take her word for it.
Oliver 如果另有其人
你现在应该装备起来
Oliver,if this were anybody
else,you'd be hooded up right now
拿着箭和他们说话
on your way to having an
arrow-side chat with them.
这不是别人 是我妈
This isn't anybody
else. This is my mother.
我了解她
And I know her.
那是什么
What's that?
这是我给Lance的手机
好让他联系帽衫侠
That is the phone that I gave to Lance
so that he could contact the Hood.
他现在让你去自首吗
Is he asking to turn yourself in?
他给Laurel了 喂
He gave it to Laurel. Hello?
- 我需要你帮助
- 所以才给你手机
- I need your help.
- That's why you have the phone.
Cyrus Vanch法律上被释放了
Cyrus Vanch was just released
from prison on a technicality.
在他律师家安顿着
Living large in his lawyer's house.
没有不正当行为的证据
There's no evidence of foul play.
但我知道他是Vanch的第一个受害者
也不会是最后一个
But I know he's just Vanch's first
victim,and he won't be his last.
为什么不求助警察
What about the police?
没有新的犯罪活动我们动不了他
They can't move on him without
evidence of new criminal activity.
Laurel 我不是收集证据的
Laurel,obtaining
evidence isn't what I do.
Vanch很危险
Vanch is dangerous.
带着手机 一会再联系
Hold on to the phone,I'll call.
Laurel需要我的帮助
Laurel needs my help.
Oliver 你是赶着去帮她...
还是逃避你母亲的真相
Oliver,are you running to help her...
or away from the truth about your mother?
我有事要忙
I have work to do.
警长
Hey,Detective?
我忙着呢 Kelton
I'm busy,Kelton.
我打赌你想听这消息
I'm pretty sure you're
going to want to hear this.
我在义务警员手机里
安装的窃听器有反应了
The bug I put in that phone
from the Vigilante just lit up.
你女儿又开始给他报信了
Your daughter's playing Maid
Marion to Robin Hood again.
你去哪里
Where you going?
Pike副队办公室
Lieutenant Pike's office.
她要是去见绿箭侠
If she's meeting with the Hood,
那就必须有特遣小队陪同
there's going to be a task
force there when she does.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 贤狼 Rosemary Ducky
校对: 安坠崖
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十三集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 13
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
我们要把这些看成是一次契机
See,we got to look at all
this as an opportunity.
Triad和Bertinelli集团缺乏领导力
The Triad and the Bertinelli
organization are leaderless.
而他们就像斯特林市的权利吸尘器
The giant sucking sound you're hearing is
the current power vacuum in Starling City,
我将把它掌握在手中
the one that I plan on filling.
你怎么说服 Triad和Bertinelli的员工
How are you going to convince
the Triad and Bertinelli's crew
他们为什么要听从你
that they should sign up with you?
这...是个好问题
Well... that's an excellent question.
我先得示威
I need to do something.
华丽丽的登场
Something spectacular.
以赢得他们的注意以及尊重
To get their attention
and earn their respect.
监狱生活让我学到很多
You know what I learned in prison?
如果你想获得尊重
那就先把最强大的人放倒
If you want to be respected,you find the
biggest guy and you put him down permanent.
我想我找到试刀目标了
I think I just found the biggest guy.
这样挺好玩的
This is going to be fun.
我把肥肥裤都穿来了
I even wore my fat pants.
肥肥裤不在我的字典里对吧
I don't want to know
what those are,do I?
是的
Nope.
工作上的事
This is work.
一会就好
It'll just be a second,okay?
- 喂
- 是我 我有消息了
- Hello?
- It's me. I have something.
能见面吗
Can you meet?
好的 哪里
Yeah,where?
Winick大楼楼顶 30分钟后见
Rooftop,Winick building. 30 minutes.
干得好 Kelton
Good work,Kelton.
好了 大伙
Okay,everybody.
都用橡胶子弹 我女儿也在场
Rubber bullets. This
is my daughter here.
她不能受到任何伤害
She cannot come to any harm.
除此之外 你们可以无所不用的
把那个射箭男拿下
But outside of that,you do whatever
needs doing to bring that archer down.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
她知道我为了抓这混蛋会不择手段
Look,she knows I'd do
anything to catch this bastard.
这是最好 也是我唯一的机会
And this is the best... it's
the only option I've got.
我和你一样渴望抓到这家伙
Look,I want to get this
guy just as badly as you do.
我只是不希望你们之间产生间隙
I just don't want to see
anything come between you two.
我警告过她 让她离这个疯子远点
I warned her. I said stay
away from this lunatic.
但她没有
She didn't.
你不觉得我也很心寒吗
You don't think that
turns a knife in my back?
希望她能想到这层
I hope she sees it that way.
收起这可怜的小眼神
Mmm,put those puppy dog eyes away.
工作上突然有些事
Something's come up at work.
不能明天再做吗
That can't wait until tomorrow?
最多一个小时 我们俱乐部见
It'll only be an hour. I
can meet you at the club.
一个小时
One hour.
最多一个半小时
An hour and a half. Tops.
Ricky做了我6年半的司机
Ricky has been driving
me for six years now.
我都不记得他请过假
I can't remember the
last time he missed a day.
谢谢你主动请缨 Diggle先生
Thank you for offering
to fill in,Mr. Diggle.
乐意效劳  Queen太太 相信我
It's my pleasure,Mrs. Queen. Believe me.
你确定我儿子不会想你吗
Are you sure my son won't miss you?
他说晚上不出门
He said he was staying
in for the evening.
你真的信他了
And you believed him?
我已经认清了
你儿子想要做私事时
It's been my experience when
your son wants some alone time,
我是想拦也拦不住的
there's not much I can do to stop him.
这让我很头疼
Much to my chagrin.
前面停车
You can stop just up ahead.
不用送我进去了
No need to escort me inside.
我一个人没事 Diggle先生
I'm fine on my own,Mr. Diggle.
好的 Queen太太
Of course,Mrs. Queen.
- Diggle先生
- Queen太太
- Mr. Diggle.
- Mrs. Queen.
我只是在找洗手间
I was just,uh,looking for the restroom.
打扰了女士们 生日快乐
Excuse me,ladies. Happy Birthday.
你好 Laurel
Hello,Laurel.
感谢你的帮助
Thank you for helping.
我帮不了太多
I couldn't do much.
Vanch的老巢守卫森严
Vanch's position is
too heavily fortified.
但我拿到了这个
But I did get this.
证明他企图取代Frank Bertinelli
Evidence he's trying to take
over the positions vacated
以及Triad位置的证据
by Frank Bertinelli
and... and the Triad.
怎么了
What's wrong?
- 这里还有别人
- 什么
- We're not alone.
- What?!
警察
SCPD!
放下武器 把手放到我们能看见的地方
Get down! Hands where we can see 'em!
- 爸
- 马上
- Dad!
- Do it now!
你要是伤她一根汗毛
You so much as leave a bruise on her,
我发誓一定让你下地狱
and I swear I will drag
you down to hell myself.
Laurel 抱歉
Laurel,I'm sorry.
Quentin 不要
Quentin,don't!
我不知道是你骗了我比较糟糕
还是差点害死我更糟
I don't know what's worse... the fact that
you lied to me or nearly got me killed!
你是绝对安全的
You were completely safe.
我在楼顶上 被一群人用枪指着脑袋
I was on a rooftop with an army of
men pointing their guns in my face!
你本来就不该出现在那里
Well,you shouldn't have been
on that roof in the first place.
不 你可希望我出现了
No! You wanted me on that roof.
这不是你埋伏的根本所在吗
Wasn't that the whole
point of your little trap?
我这是在抓杀人犯
I'm trying to catch a killer.
你利用了我
You manipulated me.
利用 根本是自己跑去找这家伙的
Manipulated? You
practically ran to this guy.
我跟你说过离他远点 但是你没有
I told you,I said stay away
from him and you did not.
- 那是在你给我电话以前
- 什么
- That was before you gave me the phone!
- What?!
在你意识到可以
用自己的女儿做诱饵之前
That's before you realized that you
could use me as bait. Your own daughter.
是啊 但是你不听我话
Yeah,but you wouldn't listen to me!
你被对他的仇恨蒙蔽了
You are so blinded by your hate for him
以致你看不见这对你的生活
that you don't realize the damage
that it's doing in your own life.
对你家人的伤害
To your family.
你抓到他又怎样
So what happens when you catch him?
然后又怎样呢 爸爸
What happens then,Dad?
你就再找一个罪犯
为母亲的离开找个发泄对象
You're going to find another criminal;
somebody else to blame for mom leaving?
还是为Sarah的死 还是你的酗酒
For Sarah dying,for your drinking?
够了 Laurel
That's enough,Laurel.
你说得对 的确够了
Yeah,you're damn right,it is.
Laurel
Laurel!
电话
The phone.
电话还给我
Give me the phone.
Laurel可能会受伤 甚至更糟
Laurel could have been hurt,or worse.
大概Lance的错吧
And I suppose that was Lance's fault.
你想说什么 Dig
What's your point,Dig?
只要是Laurel或者你妈妈的事
Just that you don't really see
straight when it comes to Laurel.
你就不能冷静对待
Or your mother.
现在不适合谈这个
This is not the time
to bring this up again.
好吧
Ok. Ok.
但有些话 我还是早说的好
But there's something I should tell you
and it's better I tell you now than later.
我给你妈妈开了好几天车
I'll be driving your mother
around for a few days.
- 你在监视她
- 我只是在尽职调查 Oliver
- You're spying on her?!
- Just doing my due diligence,Oliver.
看看她是否与我们的目标有接触
See if she meets with anyone
we might be interested in.
她不是嫌犯
She's not a suspect.
她是我妈妈
She's my mother.
所以才需要有人能客观的调查她
Which is exactly why someone needs
to take a close,objective look at her.
Oliver 这座城市背后
有巨大的阴谋 你明白的
Oliver,something's going on
in this city. You know it.
这不能说明她也参与了
That doesn't mean she's involved.
那我给她开几天车也没什么问题吧
Then there's no harm in me driving
her around for a few days,is there?
我仍然不敢相信 他把我当作诱饵
I still can't believe
it. He used me as bait!
- 谁
- 我爸
Who? My father.
他想抓住义务警员
He was trying to catch the Vigilante.
他窃听了我们的通话
He eavesdropped on my
phone conversation with him
然后就埋伏在我们约好的地点
and then lied in wait
with his jack boots.
- 今晚的事
- 是的
This was tonight? Yes.
在你工作的时候
While you were working.
这就是工作
This was work.
所以你和这个帽衫男约了见面
So you met up with the
Hood guy? Knowingly?
他以前联系过我
He's contacted me before.
Declan的案子以及Joanna的纵火案
都是他帮了我
He helped me with the Declan case
and Joanna's arson investigation.
Declan的案子是好几个月前了
The Declan case was months ago.
我知道 Tommy 我一直想告诉你
I know,Tommy,I've been
wanting to tell you.
Laurel 他是个杀人犯
Laurel,he's a murderer!
天哪 你这口气好像我爸爸
God. You sound like my father.
虽然我不想这么说 但你爸爸是对的
Well,I hate to break it
to you,but he's right.
你要站在他那边
Are you seriously taking his side?
这几个星期 他一直在骗我
He's been lying to me for weeks!
很不好受 对吧
Yeah,it feels like crap,doesn't it?
Tommy
Tommy!
昨夜斯特林市警方对臭名昭著的义务警员
展开了一场诱捕行动
A sting operation to catch the notorious
Starling City vigilante wreaked havoc last night.
虽然警方未能成功逮捕治安维持者
Despite the police's failed
attempt to apprehend the Vigilante,
警方仍强调 市民需提高警惕
police have continued to insist
that their warnings remain.
该义务警员手持弓箭 极端危险
This archer is to be
considered armed and dangerous.
如果您受到袭击 千万记得报警
Should you find yourself in harm's
way,always always,call 9-1-1.
有意思
Interesting.
用欺骗和恐吓 来扬名天下
Using deception and intimidation
to make a name for himself.
这家伙抄袭我嘛
This guy stole my move.
警署的朋友
I have news.
告诉我一个内部消息
From my friend in the police department.
我想我有办法把帽衫男引出来
I think I've figured out a way to
get the Hood out and into the open.
说来听听
Astonish me.
还记得那位律师
Remember that attorney?
Laurel Lance
Laurel Lance?
我没看错吧
Now what's wrong with this picture?
你看起来像是...在工作
You look like you're...working.
我正在筛选简历 给夜总会挑个厨师
I'm going over résumes for the
Chef's position at the nightclub.
这个看起来不错
他赢得了"最佳厨师"第六季的冠军
This guy looks pretty good.
He won "Top Chef" Season Six.
能上这个节目 厨艺肯定不错
At this point,it is basically a
culinary prerequisite to be on that show.
我可以跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you about something?
Tommy...每次你想跟我谈谈
Tommy... Every time you want
to talk to me about something
总是关于Laurel
and that something is Laurel,
你看起来就像 要告诉我你得绝症了
you look like you're about to tell
me you have a terminal disease.
她一直和帽衫男有合作
She's been working with the Hood guy.
什么
What?
你让她和那个疯子合作
她会因此受伤的 Tommy
You're letting her work with that
crazy person? She could get hurt,Tommy.
我没有"让"她做任何事 好吗
I'm not "letting" her do anything,okay?
我刚刚才发现
I only just found out about it
因为她谎言败露了
because she accidentally slipped
up on one of her many lies.
撒谎 这可不像Laurel的作风
She's lying to you? That
doesn't sound like Laurel.
谎话连篇 不告诉大家 自己跟谁在一起
Lying,keeping secrets about
who she's spending time with...
是不是很像我们认识的谁
does that remind you of anybody we know?
我 每段关系中的我
Me,in every relationship
that I've been in.
我也是 除了这段
Me,too. Except this one.
Laurel有点迷恋上了帽衫男
There's some sort of
infatuation thing going on here.
我...我们都知道
I... We both know that she has
a pretty strong track record
她过去常常被危险的人 出格的人吸引
of being attracted to guys who
are dangerous,who break the rules.
谁又能比帽衫男更危险更出格呢
Show me a more dangerous
rule breaker than the Hood.
我觉得你应该跟她好好谈谈
I just think you need to
have an honest chat with her.
找出她撒谎的真正原因
Find out the real reason
she's keeping secrets.
我只是无法相信所有人中
偏偏是Laurel会当着我的面撒谎
I just can't believe that Laurel,of
all people,would lie to my face.
我想...这是因为她是我最亲近的人
I guess that's the way that it is
with the people that you're closest to.
我知道
I know.
不管怎样 在事情变得无法收拾前
But talk to her anyway,and fix this.
跟她好好谈谈 处理好这件事
Before it becomes
something that's unfixable.
生存
Shengcun.
- 这是中文 意思是...
- 生存
- It's Chinese. It means sur...
- Survive.
你觉得他是什么意思
除了不要被杀了
What do you think he
meant,besides not getting killed?
十公里外有个机场
There's an airfield 10 clicks from here.
是离开这座岛的关键
It's key off this island.
我和姚飞观察它好几个月了
Yao Fei and I had been
observing it for months,
熟悉他们的行动
familiarizing ourselves
with their operations.
我们本该一起离开这座岛
We were supposed to get
off this island together.
但后来姚飞遭突袭 我们走散了
But then Yao Fei was
compromised,and we were separated.
这是做什么
What's this for?
姚飞派你过来 可能是...
他觉得我一个人不可能成功
I think Yao Fei sent you because he
knows I cannot take the airstrip alone.
和姚飞口气真像
Sounds like Yao Fei.
他可比我心软多了
He is a softer judge
of character than I am.
如果你要让我帮你
我得知道你能不能胜任
If you're going to have my back,I
need to know you can cover it.
愣着干嘛
What are you doing?
回击
Fight back.
拔出你的剑 千万别放手
Keep your blade up. Always
stay behind your sword.
你没有技巧 没有力量
You have no skill. No strength.
没有受过训练
No training.
说你像个娘们都太抬举你了
To say you fight like a
girl would be a compliment.
告诉过你...我不是士兵
I told you... I'm not a soldier.
游艇失事我才来了这
无意中我杀了穿这身制服的人
I was shipwrecked here. I killed the guy
that was wearing this uniform by accident.
姚飞在哪
Where was Yao Fei?
他让我快逃
He told me to run.
所以我逃了
And I did.
嗨 我是Tommy 嘟声之后请留言
Hey,it's Tommy,hit me on the beep.
嗨 又是我
Hey,it's me again.
给我回个电话吧
Please call me back.
我们应该谈谈
I think we should talk.
我正给你留言呢
I was just leaving you a message.
我喜欢有两下子的女人
I love a girl who can
take care of herself.
不过终究躲不过电击枪
But can't block a taser.
Diggle先生 不用下车了
Oh,no need to get out
of the car,Mr. Diggle.
只是去见我的会计师
It's just my accountant.
除了无聊 啥也没有
The only threat is boredom.
没关系 Queen夫人 这是我的职责
Well,it's no problem at
all,Mrs. Queen. It's my job.
嗯 你晚上放假吧
Yes. Well,then,take the night off.
我没事
I'm quite all right.
处理好了
It's taken care of.
我已经把它处理好了
I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard不是问题了
Carl Ballard will not
be a problem anymore.
你一向小心谨慎
Given your propensity for squeamishness,
我猜Ballard先生 应该还活得好好的
I'm assuming that Mr. Ballard
remains in good health.
我让他很清楚地明白了
他的计划妨碍到了我们的大计
I made it clear to him persuasively that
his plans endangered the undertaking.
我没必要威胁他吧
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
很好
Excellent.
现在 还有件事要你办
Now,one more matter to attend to.
我要你按这个地址
把里面的东西彻底销毁了
I need you to have to contents of this
address removed and disposed of thoroughly.
你存放游艇残骸的仓库
The warehouse where you're storing
the remains of "the Queen's Gambit".
我早告诉过你
我知道Robert的游艇被人动了手脚
I already told you,I knew
Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
其他人知道了蛛丝马迹可不好
And I don't think it serves for
anyone to find evidence of that.
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
没什么 只是逛逛
Nothin'. Just hangin'.
我给Queen夫人工作
I work for Mrs. Queen.
我负责她会面的那位先生的安全
And I work security for
the man she's meeting with.
我想我们是一个团队的
I guess that means
we're on the same team.
我可不这么想
把你口袋里的东西拿出来
I don't think so. And I'm going to need to
see what you put in your pocket just then.
你是什么人 警察
What are you,man,the police?
把它拿出来
Show it to me.
马上
Do it now.
好的
Right.
我只是想...可以在这抽会烟
Just thought I could come in here
and ruin my lungs a little bit.
我知道 这不是好习惯
I know,it's a filthy habit.
Laurel 是我 我们可以谈谈吗
Laurel,it's me. Can we talk?
Laurel
Laurel?
告诉义务警员 尽快
Make sure this message finds
its way to the Vigilante.
他要是不来拜访我一下
当太阳升起的时候
Do it fast,because at sunrise,I'm
going to leave pieces of this girl
我就杀了她
all over Starling City unless
he pays me a little visit.
你知道的 让我彼此了解一下
You know,gives us a chance to
get to know each other better.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
你的行动组...我不知道
他们可以追踪这个吗
Can your CSIs,I don't know,can they
track this or trace it or something?
他们怎么知道Laurel
How did he know about Laurel?
什么
What?
这个家伙怎么知道
Laurel和帽衫男有联系
How does this guy know Laurel
is connected to the Hood?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我也是昨晚才知道的
I only found out about
it myself last night.
她...她说你知道
She...she said you knew.
只有我和...
Well,just me and...
Lance先生 这个疯子抓住了Laurel
Mr. Lance,this maniac has got Laurel!
你必须召集武装队
我不知道...或者特警
You got to call in posse or
something,I don't know,SWAT teams.
我不能
I can't.
- Lance探长...
- 我要去打个电话
- Detective Lance...
- I got to go make a call.
你能来我很高兴
Thanks for coming.
在你家谈这个不是很方便
It didn't seem like a good idea
to talk about this at your house.
你怎么跟我妈妈解释
Yeah,it would have been
a little awkward for you
你在监视她 这的确有点尴尬
to explain to my mother
that you're spying on her.
不
No,man.
这才是尴尬的地方
Awkward part's coming up.
你窃听了我妈妈
You bugged my mother?
好好听着
Just listen.
处理好了
It's taken care of.
我已经把它处理好了
I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard不是问题了
Carl Ballard will not
be a problem anymore.
你一向小心谨慎
Given your propensity for squeamishness,
我猜Ballard先生 应该还活得好好的
I'm assuming that Mr. Ballard
remains in good health.
我让他很清楚地明白了
他的计划妨碍到了我们的大计
I made it clear to him persuasively that
his plans endangered the undertaking.
我没必要威胁他吧
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
很好
Excellent.
现在 还有件事要你办
Now,one more matter to attend to.
我要你按这个地址
把里面的东西彻底销毁了
I need you to have to contents of this
address removed and disposed of thoroughly.
你放置游艇残骸的仓库
The warehouse where you're storing
the remains of "the Queen's Gambit".
我告诉过你 我知道Robert的游艇
被动了手脚
I already told you,I knew
Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,man.
游艇被动了手脚
The yacht was sabotaged.
有人想要害死我爸
Somebody tried to kill my father.
你妈也参与了
And your mother was involved somehow.
你不能确定她有参与 Diggle
You do not know that
she was involved,Diggle!
你我都能确定的是 Oliver
她对此有所保密
What I do know Oliver,and so do
you,is that she kept this a secret.
要是她无所隐瞒 为何要这么做
Why would she do that if she
didn't have something to hide?
- 那是...
- 对
- Is that...?
- Yeah!
给你三秒钟 我便要切断电话
You have three seconds before I have
this line permanently disconnected.
Laurel出事了 她被绑架了
It's Laurel. She's been kidnapped.
听着 不管绑匪是谁 他会撕票的
Listen,whoever this is,he's
going to kill my daughter.
请相信我
Please believe me.
抱歉
Sorry.
这无关个人
It's nothing personal.
机场是防御重地
The airfield was a very
heavily fortified position.
我去过
I've been there.
我自己没法搞定
And I cannot take it on my own.
所以呢
So...so what?!
你要杀了我吗
Huh? You're just going to kill me?
我说了 这无关个人
Like I said... It's nothing personal.
但你要是活着 他们就会找你
But if you're alive,they will find you.
找到你 就会拷问你
直到你供出我的所在地
And if they find you,they will torture
you until you give up my location,
我可不能冒这险
and I cannot allow for that to happen.
别走 别这么做行不
Hey,don't leave! No,please
don't do this,all right?!
我不会对他们说...
I'm not going to say anything to that...
别难为自己了
Don't make it more
difficult upon yourself.
我能让你毫无感觉地死去
I can do this in a way that
you will not feel it at all.
- Steve Wilson
- Oliver Queen
- Steve Wilson.
- Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen 可能你是个斗士
Well,Oliver Queen... There might be
a fighter inside of you after all.
探长
Detective.
若这还是陷阱 后果很严重
If this is another trick,you
will not like the consequences.
我现在可不太高兴
I'm not particularly happy right now.
我恨你 恨你代表的一切
I hate you. I hate
everything you stand for.
但这个疯子绑架了我女儿
But this lunatic has my little girl.
留下一封勒索信
He left this behind as
some kind of ransom note.
他叫Cyrus Vanch
His name is Cyrus Vanch.
天呃... 如果他找不到你 就会撕票的
Jeez... He'll kill her
if he doesn't get to you.
怎样他都会撕票
He'll kill her anyway.
为什么来找我
So why come to me?
只有少部分人知道你与我女儿合作
It's a pretty tight circle that knows
about you and my daughter working together.
如果Vanch知道 是因为有人说了
If Vanch knows,it's because
someone at the precinct talked.
我不相信别人
There isn't anybody else I could trust.
Vanch在一栋大宅中
Vanch is holed up in a mansion.
那是防御重地
It's a heavily fortified position.
我去过 我自己没法搞定
I was there. I can't take it by myself.
需要你帮忙
I need your help.
我们要相互帮忙
Then I need yours.
时间快到了
Time's running out.
你朋友还没来
And still no visit from your friend.
我可能低估他对你的爱了
I might have overestimated
his fondness for you.
故意伤害
Assault with intent.
还有绑架
And kidnapping.
你这辈子就在监狱呆着吧
You're going to rot in
prison for life this time.
前提是你的帽衫朋友会来救你
That's assuming your
hooded BFF saves you.
来了也不太可能活着出去
And his chances of
survival are not so great.
他要抵挡住
He's going up against
trained men with their fingers
枪手每分钟射出的600发子弹
on the trigger of guns that
fire up to 600 rounds per minute.
我不是爱因斯坦 但也知道那挺多的
Now,I'm no Einstein,but
that is a lot of bullets.
即使他干掉那些人
房顶还有两名狙击手
And even if he were to take them out,I
have two sharpshooters on the roof.
他要是能干掉狙击手
And even if he were to get
by them,what's he going to do
还有名符其实的军队等着他
against the veritable army of sons
of bitches I've got waiting for him?
我说过 我不是爱因斯坦
Now,as I said,I'm no Einstein.
但还是能数到24的
But I can count to 24.
要是你好奇 我研究过那些新闻片段
And in case you're wondering... I was
so I studied up on my news footage...
24就是他箭袋中
24 is the exact number of
arrows he carries in his quive
箭的数量
and flechettes around his forearm.
缴了他的弓 Merida
Lose the bow,Merida.
摘了帽子
Ventilate him.
她是我女儿 我的小女儿
My daughter! My little girl!
我是义务警员 你是警察
I'm the Vigilante. You're the cop.
这不代表我要宣读他的权利
That doesn't mean I have to read
the bastard his rights,though.
Laurel 你没事吧
Laurel,are you ok?
没事
Yeah.
我没事
I'm ok.
好吧 你可以走了
All right,you're good to go.
我送你回家
I'll,uh,I'll take you home now.
我打车就好
I can take a cab.
Laurel 你受了打击 我送你回家
Laurel,you had a trauma.
I'll drive you home.
- 不要
- 怎么了
- No.
- What?
你要跟我保持距离一段时间
I'm going to need you to keep
your distance for a while.
- Laurel...
- 爸 我爱你
- Dad,I love you.
我会永远爱你
I'll always love you.
但我现在不能信你
But what I can't do
right now is trust you.
我只是在做本职工作
I was just doing my job.
我以为你至少会明白这点
I thought you'd
understand at least that.
这部分我明白的
That part I do understand.
但骗我 对我撒谎
我现在还不明白
But lying to me,using me...
It's going to take longer.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
要是我说不知道有没有事 你怎么想
What would you think
if I said I didn't know?
说明你很诚实
That you were being honest.
现在我爸拿着那电话
My father has the phone now.
我觉得短时间内他不会还给我
And I don't think he'll be
giving it back any time soon.
也许这样不错
Maybe that's good.
我没想到它会给你带来危险
I didn't see how it
would put you in danger.
我不是小孩子了
I'm a big girl.
我了解这有风险
I knew the risks.
现在我也了解了
Now I know them.
我不愿让你担着风险
And I'm not willing
to take them with you.
什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是 就此别过吧
It means good-bye.
Laurel
Laurel!
Laurel.
天啊 Laurel
Oh,my God,Laurel.
Laurel 告诉我你没事
Laurel,tell me you are okay,please.
我没事 抱歉
No,no,I'm fine,I'm fine. I'm so sorry.
没关系 只要你没事就好
No,no,it doesn't matter,just
as long as you're okay.
这不会改变你我的关系
You know,this does not change
anything between you and I.
需要两个人 才能拿下机场
It takes two men to take the air field.
你要是劝我离开岛 我就杀了你
And if you compromise my getting
off this island,I will kill you.
已经给你了第二次机会
You've had your second chance.
你我都很需要彼此
You need me just as much as I need you.
下一步做什么
So what's our next step?
训练你 好让你不拖后腿
Turning you into something
that won't get us both killed.
选一样武器
Choose a weapon.
现在就开始吗
We're starting now?
那是我的
That's mine.
你就是那个拷打我的疯子
You are the lunatic who tortured me?!
- 不 那是另一个人
- 别骗了
- No,that was another guy.
- Bull!
这面具 等于是我们的巴拉克拉法帽
This mask,it's my operational
equivalent to a balaclava.
我和搭档带着他们 做任务时保密身份
My partner and I wore them to keep our
identities classified during our missions.
你说谎
You're lying.
Fyers告诉我 这疯子是岛上的囚犯
Fyers told me this nutcase
is a prisoner on the island.
他对你撒谎了
He lied to you.
我和搭档来岛上是为了放走姚飞
My partner and I came here to free
Yao Fei and get him off this island.
我们是澳洲机密情报站的
We're A.S.I.S. Australian intelligence.
现在
Now.
你去找你的武器
You are going to find
your silver weapon.
有没有想过用剑
Have you considered a sword?
我喜欢剑
I like swords.
我向他明确过 他的计划威胁到了任务
I made it clear to him persuasively that
his plans endangered the undertaking.
没必要威胁他
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
我已经听了15次了
I've listened to this 15 times.
肯定是她的声音 Diggle
只是我不敢相信
It's definitely her voice,Diggle.
I just... I can't believe it's her.
家人是自己的盲点
We all have blind spots
when it comes to family.
是啊 Laurel今晚差点死了
Yeah. Laurel's almost
got her killed tonight.
要是Lance没骗她
Vanch绝不会知道她与我的联系
Vanch never would have known about her
connection to me if Lance hadn't have lied to her.
这教给我们 盲目信任 可能会很危险
I guess the lesson here is
blind trust can be dangerous.
我向他明确过 他的计划威胁到了任务
I made it clear to him persuasively that
his plans endangered the undertaking.
没必要威胁他
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
任务是什么
What's the undertaking?
不知道
I don't know.
但不停提到威胁 肯定不是好事
But with all this talk about
threats,it can't be good.
你提醒过我 如果她撒谎
You warned me that if
she was lying would be
定是要隐瞒她参与什么危险的事
to cover up her involvement
in something dangerous.
我得知道这任务是什么
I need to know what The Undertaking is.
你要怎么做
What are you going to do?
我还得跟我妈谈谈
I need to have another chat with my mom.
工发协调咨委会的合并
要在本周内完成
I'll need the Unidac merger
finalized by the end of the week.
我们在赶时间
We're on something of a clock here.
Moira Queen 你辜负了这座城市
Moira Queen,you have failed this city.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 贤狼 Rosemary Ducky
校对: 安坠崖
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十三集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 13
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo